Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 836. Structure of grenade, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 836)
  Side B. Continuation to side A. Another speaker gives a lecture on the relationship between Muslims and Christians and tells how Christians killed many Muslims.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ????? ??????? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ??? ?? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ???? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ??????? ??? ???????? ?????????? ???? ??? ????????? ????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 837. Worship, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 837)
  Side A.The audiotape starts with a speaker giving a lecture on worship. Dr T?a?riq al-Suwayda?n gives a lecture on stories of the Prophet. The speaker states that without understanding Prophet Mohammed's character, Muslims will not be able to understand the Qur'an. From minute 17 another speaker recites from the Qur'an 31-40 and gives a lecture on paradise. The speaker states the believers will find four doors in paradise and each door has a different use.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker gives more examples of paradise and its rivers, trees, and water.
  ????? ?????. ???? ??????? ???? ???????? ?????? ?? ??? ??????. ???? ??????? ??? ???? ????? ?? ???? ?????? ???? ? ?? ???????? ?? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ??? ?????? ???????.
  ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ????? ?? ??????? ?? ?????, ??????? ? ???????, ? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 838. Believing of the Last Day, Cica 1965-2000; 1 (Box 838)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on believing in the Last Day. The speaker states that by studying the last day, Muslims will understand what to do when it happens. The speaker reads the relevant texts from the Hadith and the Qur'an.
  Side B. A presenter who introduces the contents of the recording names the speaker as Dr T?a?riq al-Suwayda?n who gives a lecture on Signs before the Judgment day. Dr T?a?riq al-Suwayda?n starts the lecture by thanking some shuyu?kh (plural of sheikh) such ibn Ba?z, al-?Uthaymi?n, al-Sadh?a?n. and Sheikh ?Umar al-Ashqar who are very modest about their knowledge. Dr T?a?riq al-Suwayda?n states that the reason why Muslims study the signs of Judgment day is to be preparing for it by praying and fasting. The speaker also states that contemplating the universe makes faith stronger.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ??????? ?????? ?????. ???? ??????? ??? ????? ????? ????? ????? ?????? ???????? ??? ????? ??? ??? ????. ??? ??????? ?????? ???????? ???????? ?? ?????? ?????? ? ?????? ??????.
  ???? ??????? ???? ???????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??????. ??? ??????? ???????? ???? ??? ???? ????? ??? ??? ???? ???????, ? ??? ?????? ????? ????? ????? ????? ????? ????????. ???? ??????? ???? ???????? ??? ????? ?? ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ???? ?????? ??????? ??? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 839. The conflict between the Israel and the Palestine, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 839)
  Side A. The audiotape starts with the sound of a rocket. There is a conversation in Arabic and Hebrew regarding the conflict between Israel and Palestine and the possibility to make peace. Dr T?a?riq al-Suwayda?n gives a lecture on honor in which he states that honor is a feeling that fills the heart soul.
  Side B. Continuation to side A.
  ????? ?????. ??? ?????? ???? ???????. ???? ?????? ??????? ???????? ?? ?????? ??? ??????????? ????????????? ? ??? ?????? ??? ???????. ???? ??? ????????? ???? ?? ??? ??????? ?????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 840. Applying the shari??ah, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 840)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on applying the shari??ah. The speaker starts the lecture by defining the types of judges based on a Hadith.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The same speaker gives another lecture on applying the shari??ah. The speaker mentions the types of shari??ah law and states that whoever does not apply shari??ah is a non-believer.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??? ????? ??????? ????????? ??? ???? ??????? ????? ??????? ???????? ?? ????? ??????? ? ?????? ??????.
  ????? ??????/ ????? ????? ?????. ???? ??? ??????? ?????? ???? ??? ????? ??????? ??? ???? ??? ???? ?? ???? ??????? ????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 841. The reward is from the work race, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 841)
  Side A: A lecture on the concept of "reward." Towards the end of the tape, the speaker mention life in Barzakh (the state in which the souls of the deceased rest until Judgment Day).
  Side B. Continuation to side A. the speaker mentions some a story regarding the topic reward is from the work race.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 842. Prayer, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 842)
  Side A. A lecture on prayer. The speaker states that supplication is worship; he also states that Muslims should always ask God for anything. The speaker reads the relevant texts from the Hadith and verses from the Qur'an regarding supplication.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture on many topics such as the impact of televisions and adding hair implants to natural hair.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ???????. ??? ??????? ??? ?????? ?? ??????? ? ??? ????? ?? ???? ??? ???? ????? ???????. ??? ??????? ?????? ????? ? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ??????? ??? ??? ?????? ??? ????? ????????? ???? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 843. The complaint of the monotheists to their generous God, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 843)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on monotheists. The speaker gives many examples from the Qur'an and discusses earlier nations and how these showed their belief in God.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker states that saintly people are those who always remember God. Note: In side, B of the audiotape the speaker mentions the name of the Libyan president Qadhdha?fi? and his Green Book.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ???????? ??? ???? ?????? ??? ???? ??????? ????? ?? ????? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ?? ?????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ??? ?????? ???? ?????? ???? ??????. ??????: ??? ??? ???? ??????? ? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 844. Many topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 844)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on applying shari?ah law.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture on many topics. The speaker states that in Islam anyone could be a religious person unlike others religions where only certain people are knowledgeable about their belief. The speaker also states that when scholars and rulers are corrupt, the people become corrupt too.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??? ????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ??????? ??? ??? ??????.???? ??????? ??? ???????? ?? ??? ?? ???? ??? ??? ?? ????? ???????? ???? ???????? ??????. ???? ??????? ?? ???? ??????? ? ??????? ???? ???? ??? ???? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 845. Crying from fear of God, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 845)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the virtue of crying from fear of God. The speaker starts the lecture with a Hadith about laughter and crying. The speaker mentions stories about ancestors and their worship.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker gives more example of people crying from fear of God. He also states that that God does not look at our bodies but he looks at our hearts. Note: side B, seems as like the beginning of the recording.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??? ??? ?????? ?? ???? ?????? ??? ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ????? ? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ???????? ??? ?????? ?? ???? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ?? ???? ?? ???? ??? ??????? ?? ???? ??? ??????. ??????: ????? ?????? ?? ????? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 846. A lecture on multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 846)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on many topics such as integrity, fasting three days from each month and praying. The speaker states that Prophet Mohammed's mission was to implant good thoughts in people's hearts. The speaker also mentions a Hadith describing the best type of worship.
  Side B. A speaker recites from the Qur'an 3:37-77.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??? ??? ?????? ??? ?????? ? ????? ????? ???? ?? ?????. ???? ??????? ??? ????? ????? ???? ???? ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ???? ?????. ??? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ???? ??? ??? ????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ????? ?? ????? ?? ????? 37 ??? ????? 77.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 847. A lecture on multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 847)
  Side A. A lecture on multiple topics. The speaker mentions and explains the Hadith about imitating others. He also states that Muslims are following non-Muslims in everything. The speaker states that marriage in city hall is a false marriage.
  Side B. A speaker gives a comparison between Islamic law and politics. The speaker states that the separation of religion from politics leads to disbelieving government. The speaker reads the relevant texts from Hadith and the Qur'an regarding the lecture. Note: side B is supposed to be side A.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??? ?????? ??????.??? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ???? ???? ??? ????? ???? ??? ???????? ?????? ??? ???????? ?? ?? ???. ???? ??????? ??? ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ???? ????
  ????? ??????. ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??? ??????? ????????? ????????. ???? ??????? ??? ??? ????? ?? ??????? ???? ??? ??? ??????? ????? ???? ???? ??? ???? ???? ?????. ??? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ? ?????? ?? ?????? ????????? ?????? ????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 848. Sincerity in the work, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 848)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on sincerity in work. The speaker states that knowledge seekers should always have good manners and sincerity in their work for God's sake. The speaker reads the relevant texts from the Hadith and the Qur'an regarding the lecture.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker gives more examples of sincerity in work.
  ????? ?????.????? ??????? ?? ??????? ?? ?????.???? ??????? ??? ??? ???? ????? ?? ????? ????? ??????? ?????? ? ?? ???? ?? ????? ?? ???? ????. ??? ??????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ??????? ?????? ??? ????? ?????? ????????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ??? ????? ?? ??????? ?? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 849. The concern regarding life, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 849)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture regarding life. The speaker mentions a Hadith about life in the hereafter, which is just like putting your finger in the sea. The speaker states that concerns for collecting money destroy faith.
  Side B. The student Muhammad Bura?i? recites from the Qur'an 3:190-195. Another speaker gives a lecture on the attitude of the human mind towards revelation. The speaker reads the relevant texts from the Hadith regarding the lecture.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ??????? ??? ??????. ??? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ????? ??? ?????? ? ???? ??? ??? ??????? ??? ??? ????? ???? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ??? ?????? ????? ???? ???? ?? ???? ?? ?????. ???? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ????? ??? ???? ??? ???? ? ?????? ????? ????? ?????? ????????.???? ????????? ????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 850. The preservation of the minds, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 850)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the preservation of minds. The speaker states that God prohibits wine because it is not good for the body or the brain, unlike those who say that wine helps to digest food and make the body stronger. The speaker mentions that wine, alcohol, and drugs are prohibited because these corrupt the brain. Note: Tape 850(A) is a continuation of Tape 849(B).
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions many examples regarding preserving the mind.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ???????? ??? ??????
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ??? ????? ????? ?????? ????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 851. Leadership, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 851)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on rulers and people. The speaker states that if the leaders are corrupt, the people will be corrupt too. He also states that if the people are corrupt then God will send them a leader that is like them.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions an example of Israelis asking Moses how will they know if God is satisfied or will show his wrath to them.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ???? ??????? ?? ???? ?????? ???? ??? ???? ?????? ??? ??? ???? ????? ???? ??? ?? ???? ???? ????? ???? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ???? ?? ???????????? ??????? ????? ???? ?? ??? ???? ?? ??? ????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 852. Prayers, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 852)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on prayer. The speaker mentions a Hadith that encourages and urges Muslims to pray.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture on late night prayers. The speaker states that the best prayers and fasting to God is David's prayers and fasting, because it was continuous worship. The speaker mentions stories of ancestors and their worship; he also mentions the reward of the praying late night prayers.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??? ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ????? ???? ? ??? ???????? ??? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ?? ???? ????? ??? ???? ??????? ??? ???? ???????? ???? ???? ????? ? ???? ????? ???? ????? ???? ????? ?????? .??? ??????? ??? ??? ????? ?????? ? ???????? ? ??? ??? ???? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 853. The diseases of the Hearts, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 853)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the diseases of the heart. The speaker explains verse 51-52 from Su?rat al-ma??idah, "O ye who believe! Take not the Jews and the Christians for your friends and protectors". The speaker states that those who have a disease of the heart are hypocrites.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker gives more examples from the Qur'an and the Hadith about the diseases of the heart. The speaker states if the heart is mending, everything will be reformed.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ? ??? ?????? 51 ? 52 ?? ???? ???????. ???? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ??? ?? ?????????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ??? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ? ???????? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ? ???? ???? ?? ??? ????? ??? ?? ???.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 854. The governor and the people, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 854)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on leadership. The speaker states that when people are corrupt God sends a leader to misguide them.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker states that staying away from the Shari??ah law is what makes nations and people corrupt. The speaker recites the second verse from Su?rat Luqma?n. Another speaker recites from the Qur'an 17:1-28.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ??? ????? ?? ??????? ?? ???? ???? ??? ???? ????? ? ?????.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ??? ???? ???? ??? ????? ?? ??? ???????? ??? ?????. ??? ??????? ???? ????? ??????? ?? ???? ?????. ?? ????? ??????? ??? ????? ??? ???? ?? ???? ??????? ?? ????? 1 ??? ????? 28.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 855. Plans to destroy Islam, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 855)
  Side A. A colloquium starts with a recitation of the Qur'an by a student named ?Abd Alla?h Ibn Mat?ar. Sheikh ?Abd al-Rah?i?m al-T?ah?h?a?n gives a lecture on plans to destroy Islam. The speaker states that Muslims were a strong nation because they were united as one person. The same speaker states that only God knows the secrets of souls. He also mentioned that the soul of a fetus is different.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker states that the soul exists, but humans cannot see it. He also states that happiness does not come from money but from faith and the best faith is the understanding that God is with you all the time. The speaker answers questions from the audience regarding religious issues such as the difference in the Islamic doctrines and verses from the Qur'an that should be read on Fridays.
  ????? ?????. ????? ????? ???? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ??? ???? ????? ????? ?? ???? ???? ?? ???? ??? ?????? ?????? ?????? ?? ???????? ?????? ??? ??????? ???? ???? ??? ???????? ????? ?????? ????? ????? ???? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ???? ?????? ??? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ??? ????? ?????? ???? ?? ???? ???? ??????? ? ???? ??? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ????? ?? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 856. Sleeping, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 856)
  Side A. The audiotape starts with a recitation of the Qur'an 17:78-88. Another speaker gives a lecture on sleeping. The speaker states that we spend one third of our lives sleeping; he also mentions that only God does not sleep. The speaker mentions a story by Luqma?n (a wise man from pre-Islamic times) regarding sleeping.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions stories regarding sleeping and dreams. He also states that Muslims should sleep early so they can wake up early and pray.
  ????? ?????. ??? ?????? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ????? ??????? ???? ????? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ???? ???? ??? ??????? ???? ??? ???? ?? ????? ? ??? ????? ????? ?? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ??? ??? ?? ????? ? ?????? ??????? ? ??? ???????? ??? ?????? ?????? ??? ???????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 857. Pursuing the right path, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 857)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on pursuing the right path. The speaker mentions a Hadith that states that every hundred years God sends a man to rejuvenate religion. The speaker states that we have to follow the path of the ancestors
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions more examples of ancestors and how they followed the right path.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ??????. ??? ??????? ????? ?????? ?? ?? ???? ???? ?? ???? ???? ????? ?? ??? ???. ???? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ?????? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ??? ????? ?? ????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 858. [Duplicate of Tape 856], Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 858)
  Side A. [Duplicate of Tape 856, Side A].
  Side B. [Duplicate of Tape 856, Side B].
  ????? ??????. .[??? ?????? ??? 856, ????? ??????].
  ????? ?????. .[??? ?????? ??? 856, ????? ?????]
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 859. Integrity, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 859)
  Side A. Sheikh ?Abd al-Rah?i?m al-T?ah?h?a?n gives a lecture on integrity. The speaker defines the word integrity and its meaning, the place that people of integrity have with God, and the advice of ancestors regarding integrity.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. the speaker reads the relevant texts from the Qur'an that urge Muslims show integrity.
  ????? ?????. ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?? ????????? ??? ???? ???? ?????? ?????????? ??? ???? ? ??? ????? ????? ?????? ??????????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ?????? ??? ????? ?? ?????? ???? ??? ???????? ??? ?????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 860. [Duplicate of Tape 845], Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 860)
  Side A. [Duplicate of Tape 845, Side B].
  Side B. [Duplicate of Tape 845, Side A].
  ??? ?????? ??? 845, ????? ??????].]
  ????? ??????. .[??? ?????? ??? 845, ????? ????? ]
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 861. Ethics of Visiting, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 861)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the ethics of visiting. The speaker states that Muslims should follow etiquette when visiting others, especially by visiting them at an appropriate time.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions stories of ancestors and how they visited each other.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ???? ??????? ??? ???? ??????? ???? ?????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ??? ??? ????? ?????? ? ??? ????? ?????? ????? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 862. The position of the human mind from the divine revelation, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 862)
  Side A. The audiotape starts with a recitation of the Qur'an by a student named Muh?ammad al-Bura?i?. Sheikh ?Abd al-Rah?i?m T?ah?h?a?n gives a lecture on the position of the human mind in divine revelation. The speaker discusses the types of the human mind, corruption, and deviation from the right path.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions examples regarding the topic from Hadith and the Qur'an.
  ????? ?????. ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ??????????? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ? ?????? ? ???????? ?? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ?????? ???????? ?????? ???????? ?? ?????? ?????? ? ????? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 863. Ways of Satan aspirant astray slaves, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 863)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the ways Satan leads slaves astray. The speaker discusses the ways Satan takes people from God's path to his path.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions examples of the ways Satan make people become disbelievers.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?????? ??? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ?????????? ???? ??????? ?? ??? ??????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ????????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ????? ?? ??? ??????? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 864. Piety, Circa 1976-2000; 1 (Box 864)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on piety. The speaker states that the companions of the Prophet Mohammed always showed great ethics and piety in their learning circles. Another speaker recites from the Qur'an 31:1-34. Note: This lecture was given to the women in the audience.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture on the sincerity of knowledge seekers.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ??????. ??? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ? ?????? ?? ????? ?????. ???????? ??? ???? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ????? 1 ??? ????? 34.
  ????? ??????. ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ???? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 865. Types of worships, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 865)
  Side A. A lecture on the different types of worship. The speaker states that God classified worship. Each type of worship has a great impact on the soul and ethics.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions that God imposed the pillar of fasting on past nations. He also mentions a Hadith about the virtue of fasting and its impact on the soul and ethics.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ????????. ???? ??????? ??? ???? ???? ???????? ???? ?? ???? ??? ????? ??? ??? ?? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ????? ????? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ??? ???? ??? ?????? ??? ????? ???????. ??? ??????? ?????? ????? ?? ??? ?????? ???? ???? ??? ?????? ?? ???? ???? ??? ????? ? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 866. Different types of worships, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 866)
  Side A. A lecture on the ethics of visiting. The speaker states that visiting has an etiquette that must be followed.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions some Hadith regarding the virtues of visiting.
  ????? ?????. ????? ??????? ?? ???? ???????. ???? ??????? ??? ??????? ??? ???? ??? ???????.